Today I would be explaining to you how to make a garment bag.
The one that we are making today would be for a young girl who might be carrying her clothes back and forth to a friends house or to visit with grandmother or something.
She might want to cover up what she is taking so it would not get dirty.
This is the fabric that we would be using today; a nice bright color for a young girl.
But other choices that you might want to consider, these are other varieties of the bright colors but a solid color would work well.
Denim would work well that would be fine for a young man to carry his clothes in if it was denim.
Canvas would also work well.
Any sort of print, any kind of trim, something to keep the clothes from getting dirty.
Also sorority girls seem to like something to cover all the garments that they need from one event to the next.
It would make a nice gift for someone so these are nice ideas for gifts for people of all ages both male and female.